That's why I'm here to give you a warning.
We are going to exhaust every legal remedy
to bring Florence back to her real family.
So you can be returned to us, the Almeros.
So, this is not the last time
you're going to see me.
And please...
don't do anything
that will put you in danger.
Or should I tell the Almeros
to stop bothering us
and just let me be
because I'm not their missing granddaughter?
I'm not an Almero.
I'm a Dela Cruz and that's the real me.
That's the truth I believed, Nero.
So whether we like it or not,
we need to recognize the fact
that she grew up
with a different identity,
with a different family.
Secondly, she must come to us on her own.
She should voluntarily come to us,
because if we force her,
the more she'll resist being an Almero.
You heard what Don Rogelio said, right?
They won't stop until they get you back.
We won't easily give in, Florence.
We're not related but you're still my child.
We're one family here.
You're connected to our hearts.
I'm the cause of this problem,
that's why I can find a way to solve this.
I noticed the first time I saw Florence
that she looks kind of familiar.
She had this uncanny resemblance
to the late Alyanna Almero.
Still, it's unbelievable...
that the missing daughter of Lorenzo
is Florence Dela Cruz.
Did you agree?
Do I have a choice?
I already talked to Grandpa Garp.
And we have really good lawyers.
We can help Ms. Lydia and Mr. Federico.
Do you think I want to include
the Ferells in this mess?
And based on the history
of both our families...
I don't think it's good for you
to be involved with my problem right now.
That's why you'll just agree?
You'll agree to turn your back
on the life you've been living?
Do you think I want this?
Do you think
I'm not having a hard time deciding on this?
But what can I do?
The moment I became an Almero,
I have to accept the big changes in my life.
I didn't ask this for myself.
And I didn't wish for this complication,
Nero.
But I must recognize it.
Because no matter what I do...
I can't escape from it.
That's why, Nero...
I hope you'll understand my decision.
I hope you'll understand
that I need to do this.
But what can I do?
The moment I became an Almero,
I have to accept the big changes in my life.
I didn't ask this for myself.
And I didn't wish for this complication.
But I must recognize it, Nero,
because no matter what I do...
I can't escape from it.
I hope you'll understand my decision.
I hope you'll understand
that I need to do this.
How's the food?
It's okay.
We're sorry
that we weren't able to give you a proper welcome.
We just need to do a lot of things
in the office.
But if you need anything, just call Baste.
He'll take care of everything.
There will be some changes here.
What?
You need to look and act like an Almero.
What do you mean?
Now that you're living with us, you know...
we have to transform you into someone worthy
to be called an Almero.
Go ahead and eat.
Mr. Baste...
Are those my things?
What are you going to do?
I'm replacing all your old clothes
with new ones.
Outfits that suit you better.
And as for this,
let's change this to a newer model
with more secure connection.
Baste, you take care of that.
Ms. Celestina, today we will be
fixing your posture.
Please look ahead.
Look ahead.
We will be correcting your back posture.
Okay, get a book.
On top of your head.
Chin up, shoulders down, stomach in.
And one foot over the other,
gracefully and start.
One foot over the other, gracefully.
With great timing. One more time.
Again, from the top. Let's go.
Book on your head.
Shoulders, and back straight, stomach in.
Again.
One... two... From the top.
Mr. Baste, let's eat.
Go ahead, Ma'am, it's okay.
You know, it's fun to eat
if you have companions.
How about your co-workers?
Maybe they want to eat too.
Just go ahead, they've eaten already.
Hello.
Yes, so what's the pitch?
Main offer?
Try to get a better one.
Yeah.
Hold on, hold on... Yes?
Okay, go ahead.
I just have to take this call.
Hello.
Hold on...
If you want, next week,
let's make plans with your grandfather.
Let's go out of town.
Not this week, I'm really busy, okay?
All right.
Hello.
Yes, yes. Let's finish it this week.
I will knock, knock and knock
until he opens the door.
If he refuses to open the door,
I will destroy it.
If I need to sneak into the house
or peek through the window
so he'll let me in,
I'll do it.
If I need to shout, I will shout...
Hey, let me in your heart!
Hey, let me in your heart.
Let me in!
For this kind of beauty you're not expecting,
like me.
If he still refuses to let you in,
I don't know how else.
You're asking what my favorite fruit is.
It's rambutan.
Hey, don't be noisy.
As if I'm a stranger to you
when you go to me every morning
to bring messages.
You're surprised.
I know your boss' secret.
He thinks he's the only one capable
of sending secret messages.
If he's sending secret messages,
I give secret fruits.
Rambutan.
You owe me.
How much?
Do I have to pay for your cabin?
I don't need your money.
Huh?
So what do I owe you?
You owe me three P's.
Three P's?
Pantawid Pangkabuhayan Program?
What I mean is, you owe me three favors.
Three favors?
Yes.
When the time comes
that I need a favor from you,
you can't refuse.
No questions asked.
You'll just help me
with the favors that I need from you.
What kind of favor?
Anything.
As in anything?
Yes.
Anything.
That's enough.
It's impossible that you saw her yesterday,
so that's not true.
What makes you say that?
Because we were together yesterday.
She's my girlfriend.
What?
Shall we, my Chummy pie?
Lie down.
Lie down, here.
I said lie down.
Lie down.
Just wait. Excuse me.
There you go.
Are you ready?
I said, are you ready?
I'll count to three.
One, two, three.
- You pervert!
- Hey, what's that?
- You're crazy!
- Ouch.
- You pervert! You're planning something!
- What do you mean?
- I'm planning something?
- You're planning something bad.
- What?
- Wait, wait...
Just calm down. Okay, just calm down.
- Calm down.
- What is it?
Wait, here it is.
What do you have in there?
- You will kill me?
- I don't have any evil plans.
Wait. I'm not planning something bad. Here.
What's that?
- There
- There.
There.
Orionids meteor shower.
Those are remnants of the Halley's comet.
Imagine, the last time we saw Halley
was in 1986.
But even right now now,
we can still feel its presence.
I hope I have that impact
on the person I love.
That even if I'm no longer around...
she will still remember
the beautiful memories I left for her.
Is it beautiful?
It's beautiful.
Beautiful.
Yes, it's beautiful.
Go ahead and see if it's beautiful.
Okay.
It's really beautiful.
Yes, it's so beautiful.
Let's share.
Okay, you can use the other side.
I hope you like it.
Is that special delivery?
Thank you, Nero.
I know you're always there for me.
Thank you for the falling star.
How is she?
We haven't talked to each other.
Why, did you fight?
We didn't.
I tried to call her but she cannot be reached.
She really can't be reached
because she's not just rich,
she is very rich.
Too early?
Yes.
Okay.
Maybe her signal is weak in Almero's mansion.
I don't think so.
If they don't have a 5G signal,
at least they have WiFi in the mansion.
I don't think
it's a matter of WiFi or signal.
Knowing Rogelio...
They took away Florence's cell phone.
Why would they do that, Grandpa?
You must understand, Nero,
that the Almeros are a very proud family.
They are one of the oldest families.
And they are very sensitive
with their reputation.
And now that Florence is with them,
I'm sure she's going to be changed
and become an Almero.
And this change is not
just going to be physical.
Unfortunately, this means
Florence now is being forced
to forget the life that she had.
She is now an Almero
and she needs to forget
her life being a Dela Cruz.
- What's taking them so long?
- They're coming.
- Huh?
- Don't be impatient.
They'll come.
What time is it?
You don't have a watch.
- Hey, Dencio.
- Hey, Federico and Lydia.
Thank you for coming here.
Welcome!
- Welcome!
- Go ahead and repeat it.
Repeat it.
Are you sure about what you're saying?
Yes, maybe you're just scamming us.
Don Ferell's offer is not a scam.
It was he who asked for you
to be the cook here in the mansion.
As a matter of fact,
it wasn't Don Ferell who said it.
The person who said this was...
Mother, Father.
- Nero.
And we are back.
Welcome back to GU TV
with a capital G for you and me.
So, fellow G's, how was your academic break?
Were you able to do something worthwhile?
Actually, you know what,
Gyronella is so unique.
And one of the things that makes us unique
is that we have an academic break
for students
because it truly is the belief
of our founding fathers and mothers
that the best way to shape a young mind
is to set them free
from the confines of the classroom.
Which begs the question...
Why are we paying thousands and
thousands of pesos in tuition fees
if we'll learn a lot of things
from going out?
But that is not the question
that needs answering
because the more important question is,
what's the G?
And the biggest G of our university now
sounds like the biggest plot point
of a novel.
Are you guys ready?
Rumor has it
that the Communication Arts Representative
is the only daughter
of one of the most influential families...
The Almeros!
Are you guys surprised?
Because I am... OMG!
You know buddy, it's okay here.
The benefits here are good.
You have SSS.
GSIS.
And DSWD.
See, there are a lot of benefits here.
Include the benefit of the doubt too.
Hey...
Grandpa.
Don Ferell, thank you very much
for your offer.
Yes, we just need a little distraction
because there are a lot of memories at home.
That's why, thank you very much, Don Ferell.
Buddy, just call Don Ferell Grandpa Garp.
Yes, a lot of people might hear you
and think that Don Ferell is an old man
in an old drama series.
Welcome to the house.
You know,
we're excited to taste your brand of cooking.
Yes, if you don't mind my saying.
We expect a lot from you
because Florence has set the bar too high.
I'm sorry. I didn't mean it.
That's okay, Ma'am Serafica.
We just miss Florence.
Nero, were you able to talk to Florence?
I can no longer call her at her old number.
I think she changed her number.
Maybe she's just busy,
that's why she wasn't able to call, right?
Yes.
I'm sure there are a lot of changes
in her life.
But don't worry.
The academic break will be over soon,
and I'm sure we'll see each other in school.
I'll keep you updated.
Let's go together.
Well, well, well.
Troy still looks fun.
You said it.
Excuse me, girls, but Troy is off-limits.
- Oh.
- Okay.
By the way, how was your trip
with Tristan to Seoul?
Well, we were shining through the city
with a lot of fun and soul.
The only thing I can say is, it is dynamite!
Speaking of dynamite, here is mine.
It's Aldus.
You're saying "mine" as if...
why do you have a title already for him?
How about Owen?
It seems like he's handling things
pretty well.
Ooh...
Why are you smiling like that?
Do you like Owen?
Of course not.
I'm avoiding things like that
ever since everything that happened
between Nero and I.
Speaking of Nero,
do we have news about Florence?
Is it true
what's happening between her and the Almeros?
I can't wait to talk to Florence
to know the deal.
Me too.
Florence, can we talk?
Can we talk later?
I'll find a way to talk to you.
We're your friends, Florence.
We're not a threat.
Are you okay?
- Are they treating you well?
- Hey Mister, that's enough.
Hey, that's enough.
Mister, they're not my enemies.
- Don't do that.
- Don't!
I said don't push us.
Let's go.
Oh my God, there's trouble.
What's happening?
I don't know the full details,
but what I heard...
is that her father and grandfather think
that she's in danger,
that's why security is so tight around her.
Why? Why would she be in danger?
Yeah?
Back in the day,
somebody tried to murder her and her mother.
So since the case of her real mom
is still unsolved,
that's probably why the Almeros are taking
great safety precautions
for her.
See?
Do you see
how troublesome the Ferell guys are?
This is symptomatic of who they are.
They don't have respect.
They think the whole Levante is their kingdom
and that they own everything.
Maybe there was just miscommunication.
And you even managed to defend them.
So who's at fault here?
Is it you?
Should you be blamed
for everything that happened?
Lorenzo...
Celestina, you have to understand...
you shouldn't trust the Ferells!
But I lived with them for a long time,
that's why I'm close to them.
And we're going to the same school.
I will still encounter them no matter what.
You're right.
You can't avoid them.
So I think it's about time
that I transfer you to a different school.
Look, let's not overreact, Lorenzo.
The school started already,
it'll be such a pity
if you waste what Florence has started in GU.
Maybe we just have
to make Florence understand...
that you have to cut all ties
with the Ferells.
Because a Ferell is never good news
to this family.
I'm not naive.
I know all
about you and that Ferell boy, Nero.
Yes, your grandfather told me
about your shenanigans during the ball.
Is he your boyfriend?
It doesn't matter.
Because I will never allow that relationship.
And I will never accept a Ferell
to be a part of this family!
Now, if you refuse to listen to me
and continue your relationship
with the Ferell guy,
I will pull you out of your university
and send you abroad.
I have good news for you.
Wait, it seems my timing is wrong.
I'm sorry if I intrude on this family matter.
Okay, I'll just come back...
No, no, just stay, Samuel.
Lorenzo is done already.
And I want an update on the dealings
with the Marquezes.
Go to your room.
Think carefully about what I told you.
I'm very disappointed with you, boys.
What went into your minds to fight with them?
Ms. Serafica, we only wanted
to talk to Florence.
And you too, you're the eldest.
You should've recognized the situation.
Are you all aware of what I mean?
Florence's situation is different now.
We all should be aware of the fact
that she's an Almero.
And we're the Ferells.
And this kind of incident
would only complicate our relationship
with Florence.
Boys, you have to be careful.
There are a lot of changes in her life.
You know, I could feel what you're feeling.
She's close to us, right?
But I hope we won't add
to what she's going through right now.
That's right!
Violence is never the answer.
That's why give chance a peace.
Give peace a chance.
That's the same.
How's the fight, boys?
Did you do it?
Did you do what I asked you to do?
Of course, Grandpa.
I'm really disappointed, Don Ferell.
Do you believe that violence is the answer?
You're not giving a chance a peace.
Give peace a chance.
I said that's the same.
Are you really consenting your grandchildren
to become violent?
I am also disappointed.
As my father figure and my boss,
I am very, very disappointed.
Didn't you tell them?
Huh?
Of course, I will not tolerate violence.
The trouble earlier was all part of a plan.
Oh?
Plan.
What plan?
Hello.
Hello, Florence.
- Surprise!
Nero?
Is that you?
And am I hearing the right thing?
Yes, it's me.
We're all complete, plus the four fools.
And Ms. Serafica and Grandpa Garp.
Wait, how were you able
to put the phone in my bag?
Are they treating you well?
- Don't push!
- What's with you?
- Hey!
- Mister, they are my friends.
- They're not my enemies.
- Stop it, mister.
- Enough!
- Ouch!
- Stop it!
- That's enough!
- Stop!
Do you think
I will just let them take you away from me?
Did you see my moves earlier?
That was nothing.
That's no match with my muscles.
We did all of that for you, Florence.
I'm so impressed with you,
and I'm so touched by your efforts.
Really?
You're so touched?
As in touched for the very first time?
Fool.
Florence.
Grandpa Garp.
Before Nero talks to you in private,
we'd like you to know
that you're always in our hearts and minds.
You're always in our hearts and minds.
It should be,
because if I'm not in your hearts and minds,
I'll feel bad.
We will never give up on you.
I would like to apologize
for the stressed caused
by the commotion earlier.
At first, I was hesitant,
but we needed to find a way to talk to you.
I told you,
you're already part of this family,
and we will not easily give up on you.
Florence, were you able
to eat properly there?
Yes, Ma'am Serafica, don't worry.
They have a cook here,
but she's not as good as Mother and Father.
But it's okay.
Florence,
this is Dencio.
What, is someone fighting with you there?
No, Mr. Dencio. I'm the bully here.
That's good to hear, Florence,
because if not,
I'll send a reinforcement there.
Hey this guy,
you're sending a reinforcement that soon?
Actually, Florence, there's still someone
who wants to talk to you.
Who? Is that Mr. James?
Is he eating your ham?
Tell him it's okay
as long as he's eating a half cup of rice.
Or is it Ms. Patotina?
Is she taking care of Ma'am Serafica?
Hello, Florence.
Why?
Do you miss me already?
Nero, we need to talk.
How was your sleep? Is it okay?
The truth is,
I wasn't able to sleep last night.
I keep thinking about what Don Ferell said.
We should find out who killed Alyanna.
Don't you remember anything, Federico?
Anything?
Just a little.
Maybe I can remember
the shape of the head, the shape of his eyes.
If there's a suspect,
they make a drawing, right?
Yes, that's right. There's a name for that.
Cartographic sketch artist.
Yes, that's the one.
Why do you need to talk to me
if I didn't do anything bad?
It's because
someone wants to talk to you, Florence.
Is it true that you have something to do
with what happened to Mommy?